{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Fence Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/61740/":{"taskOID":61740,"originalTaskOID":61740,"setID":8082,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5554,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200206,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200205,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install a new fence ","answerDisplayText":"Install a new fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502305,"questionDisplayText":"Fencing material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of fencing material do you want to install or repair?","shortQuestionText":"What type of fencing material do you want to install or repair?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203185,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl or PVC","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl or PVC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203184,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chain Link","answerDisplayText":"Chain Link","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203186,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wrought Iron","answerDisplayText":"Wrought Iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203187,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Aluminum or Steel","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum or Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203188,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Barbed Wire","answerDisplayText":"Barbed Wire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203189,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Electric Pet Fence","answerDisplayText":"Electric Pet Fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500140,"questionDisplayText":"Length of Fence","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately, how many linear feet of fencing do you need? ","shortQuestionText":"Approximately, how many linear feet of fencing do you need? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200202,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 200 feet","answerDisplayText":"100 - 200 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200203,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"201 - 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"201 - 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200200,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"Over 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5554,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200206,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200205,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install a new fence ","answerDisplayText":"Install a new fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200206,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200205,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install a new fence ","answerDisplayText":"Install a new fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502305,"questionDisplayText":"Fencing material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of fencing material do you want to install or repair?","shortQuestionText":"What type of fencing material do you want to install or repair?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203185,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl or PVC","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl or PVC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203184,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chain Link","answerDisplayText":"Chain Link","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203186,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wrought Iron","answerDisplayText":"Wrought Iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203187,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Aluminum or Steel","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum or Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203188,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Barbed Wire","answerDisplayText":"Barbed Wire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203189,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Electric Pet Fence","answerDisplayText":"Electric Pet Fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203185,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl or PVC","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl or PVC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203184,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chain Link","answerDisplayText":"Chain Link","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203186,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wrought Iron","answerDisplayText":"Wrought Iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203187,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Aluminum or Steel","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum or Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203188,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Barbed Wire","answerDisplayText":"Barbed Wire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203189,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Electric Pet Fence","answerDisplayText":"Electric Pet Fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500140,"questionDisplayText":"Length of Fence","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately, how many linear feet of fencing do you need? ","shortQuestionText":"Approximately, how many linear feet of fencing do you need? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200202,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 200 feet","answerDisplayText":"100 - 200 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200203,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"201 - 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"201 - 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200200,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"Over 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200202,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 200 feet","answerDisplayText":"100 - 200 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200203,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"201 - 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"201 - 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200200,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"Over 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/61740/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":61740,"taskName":"Fence - Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Install or Repair Fence","xmTaskDescriptor":"Fence Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"fence fencing wood picket wooded","textMessagingName":"Inst rpr fence","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes digging holes, setting posts \u0026 building sections or attaching pre-made sections.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes rail, board, slat, stockade, picket, estate, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Repair a Fence.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e Fence Installation | Repair Fences \u003cin_city\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":"Fence repair is a fairly easy project that can significantly add to the appeal of your home. The first task in fence repair is to decide what materials, such as wood panels or aluminum sheets, need to be fully replaced or just patched up. Then, remove the damaged areas thoroughly, obtain new materials that match the original, and simply exchange the new for the old. Another small fix often overlooked in fence repair is applying a new coat of paint, which can easily add a lot of visual attraction with little cost or effort.","pwcId":30,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Fence - Install or Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Fence - Install or Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Fence Project","urlName":"Fencing-Install-Repair","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"Install Fence in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fence Repair","searchKeywords":"fence,fencing,wood,picket,wooded,yard,gate","emcCategoryOid":-12030,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8082,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}